zeendo.com 2016-12-05

# Privacy Policy

## Zeendo Privacy Policy

Last updated on November 21st 2014

Thank you for visiting ZEENDO. This policy will inform you about all the questions related to the registration and usage of all the personal data facilitated by clients and users through our website or by contracting our services.

ZEENDO (Onbile SL) is the sole owner of the information collected by us at [www.zeendo.com](http://zeendo.com/). All the information given by users through the platform will not be shared or given to third parties other than service providers, nor will it be treated differently than in the ways explained in this Privacy Policy.

The Spanish version of this Privacy Policy is the final version for legal purposes. This translation into English is merely informative.

###  **1\. Information Collection and Use.**

All and any data furnished to Zeendo by the user when filling in the forms included in it will be processed by automated means and incorporated to Zeendo’s files, called “user-client”, which have been properly registered in the Spanish Data Protection Agency.

### 1.1 Registration

In the course of using the Service, we will ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and manage your account ("Personal Information"), as well as to enable you to access certain restricted parts of the Site and the Service.

ZEENDO Service requires a Login in order to provide you with a personalized account. During your account registration process, we will collect a login name, a password, and an email address from you. You must provide all of this information in order to obtain an account. After completing our registration form, you will receive a welcome email with details of your new ZEENDO account and how to access it. By submitting all this data, the user agrees to its treatment and use.

In addition, all the personal data submitted through our social networks (Facebook, Twitter, etc.) will be processed by automated means and incorporated to Zeendo’s files. In this case, registering and treating this data by automated has the purpose of enabling our communication with the user through social networks. Due to the social network or platform’s nature, the user agrees to the treatment of their data for advertising and commercial purposes related to Zeendo services and products, including the sending of electronic newsletters.

### 1.2 Use of the personal data submitted by the user.

All the personal data provided by the user and collected by us from any of our services can be used to identify potential cases of abuse and to establish statistical information about website traffic. This statistical information is not added in such a way that any given user of the system may be identified from it.

ZEENDO (Onbile SL) is the sole owner of the information collected at [www.zeendo.com](http://zeendo.com/).

Personal Information is used for the following purposes: (i) to provide the Service, (ii) to manage the use of the Service and products registered by the user (iii) to provide to you service announcements, offers and any other type of information about the service and from third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting (such as newsletters or marketing or promotional materials, on behalf of, and according to, instructions from a third party, such as our advertising partners), (iv) to enforce our Terms of Service, (v) to contact you to obtain feedback from you regarding the Site and the Service.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such announcements, information or offers, please follow the instructions to unsubscribe provided in the communication.

### 1.3 Registration, treatment and use of other non-personal data.

When the user accesses the website or uses the Service, we automatically collect certain information related to the use of the service and their activity on the website. We also register the information submitted by the user browser when visiting a website or an online service (registration details), such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring page, searches, navigation cookies, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data, among others.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements around the Site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, but this information is never used to identify users individually.

This information may also be used to identify users who are using the service for SPAM or other activities that may conflict with our Terms of Service. This information will be used as a whole, and never linked back to any personally identifiable information.

We use the information that is not Personal Information for the above purposes and also in order to (i) monitor and analyze the use of the Service and the technical management of the Site, (ii) improve the Site and the Service, (iii) generate and obtain useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behaviour of our users, and (iv) verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

### 1.4 Information related to the account's subscription.

If you choose to use the Service in the form of a paid account, Zeendo will collect personally identifiable information and store this information in the file called "user-client" in our secure server in order to process your invoices. This information will only be used to verify credit card authenticity and to issue invoices, as stated in your service agreement.

Under no circumstances will this information be given or transmitted to outside third parties.

### 1.5 Data submitted by users to other websites

Zeendo explicitly informs that we do not have control over third parties' websites or over information, banners, adverts, links or similar means that register or ask for personal information about the user (cookies, data, etc.).

The collection and use of such information and access to third party websites are subject to such third parties' privacy policies. Zeendo encourages you to read the privacy policies and other terms of such third parties' websites before using their services.

### 1.6 Minor's personal information.

As stated in the [Service Terms of Use](http://zeendo.com/terms-of-service), the user must be at least 18 years old and legally able to use the Service, and it will be assumed that the user complies with these requirements.

If a parent or guardian becomes aware that their child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, they can contact us at [www.zeendo.com/contact-us](http://zeendo.com/contact-us), to exercise their right to access, rectify, cancel or object to this information, as established by the applicable law.

###  **2\. ARCO rights (access, rectification, cancellation and objection)**

Users can exercise their right to access, rectify, cancel and object to this information, as established by the current applicable legislation on data protection.

For these purposes, they will need to send a signed request to Zeendo, at the following address: Avda. Cortes Valencianas nº 26. Bloque I. Escalera 1 Entlo. 2, Oficina 2, CP. 46015 Valencia (Spain), or send the original written and signed request (scanned) via email to [help@zeendo.com](mailto:help@zeendo.com). The request must include the following information:

* Requester's identity: Full name and a photocopy of their identity card or proof of identity by other valid means.
* Address for notification purposes, date and requester's signature.
* Application with details of the request (access, cancellation, rectification and objection). If the rights to rectify or cancel are to be exercised, the requester must specify the information to be modified and in what way.
* Documents supporting the request.

If the request is made through a third party, as explained before, the requester must also submit proof of representation accreditation and power of attorney.

### 2.1 Access to Personally Identifiable Information.

Zeendo is responsible for the client's personally identifiable information file and its treatment, as well as for the information retrieved in connection with their registration process.

When the user purchases or contracts the Service, the system provides them with a "line of codes" to manage the transaction. If it is Zeendo who, following the user's request, manages the transaction directly, the user expressly consents and authorizes Zeendo to access their server.

Notwithstanding the above, Zeendo, as "responsible for processing," will perform this tasks according to the instructions of the client-user, whom will be the sole responsible for the treatment of the data introduced or modified by them, thus exonerating Zeendo for all responsibility in case the client-user violates the Data Protection laws.

### 2.2 Rectification or modification of data.

All user information stored at Zeendo related to a user account, including any subscription billing information, is accessible through the Site's administration panel of each user. 

Users may modify, update or rectify the information provided through the Site at any time, and we encourage you to keep this information up to date so that your customer service requests and billing processing operate efficiently.

### 2.3 Cancellation of data.

Users can delete their personal information, provided that it is not mandatory by law otherwise, or due to legitimate business purposes. 

In order to do so, users must proceed in the way explained in the "ARCO rights" section above, and comply with the requirements established regarding application, content and address to submit the request.

In addition, Zeendo may delete any information provided by you or related to you, pursuant to our policies valid at the time or the current applicable law.

###  **3\. Safety measures.**

We employ a variety of measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. All the data submitted by clients and users is registered and stored on servers and files of the company, and they are protected and registered according to the current legislation.

Zeendo has basic technical and organizational measures, which are required by the current legislation according to the nature of the data stored on its files. These measures guarantee the security of the personal information treated by the company, avoiding its alteration, loss or non- authorized access, according to the technology state in every moment, the nature of the personal data stored and the possible risks to which are subject.

In addition, the company guarantees the confidentiality of all the data submitted by the user, but they can be revealed to the competent authority in those cases established by law.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send us a support request using our support system or an email to [help@zeendo.com](mailto:help@zeendo.com).

### 3.1 Safety measures responsibility of the user-client.

Zeendo will not be responsible for the data registered by third parties through websites hosted in Zeendo's servers. The user-client is the responsible for fulfilling with the security measures required by the nature of the personal data registered, all in accordance with the current applicable legislation.

The user-client can contact Zeendo in case they need technical support to adopt additional safety measures to support data treatment through the user-client's website, being aware that Zeendo may have to charge them for any additional costs incurred in.

### 3.2 Information on computer attacks.

Zeendo informs you of the existence of computer and hack attacks, and of attempts to access the information on websites illegitimately. Zeendo advises users against providing sensitive personal information which is not requested and is unnecessary to engage and operate the Service.

If you receive an email asking you to update your Personal Information, do not reply and please contact us at [www.zeendo.com/contact-us](http://zeendo.com/contact-us).

###  **4\. Transferring data to third parties.**

Zeendo employs third-party service providers to perform functions on its behalf, such as enabling, providing and managing the Service or the Site, by means of maintenance, payment processing, hosting, database management, website analytics or administration, among others.

These third-party service providers have access to the personal information needed to perform their functions, but they are not allowed to use it for any other purposes, and are obliged to comply with this Privacy Policy.

In addition, Zeendo informs you that we may share your account information if needed to comply with the applicable law, enforce it or enforce our Service Terms of Use, or to protect the rights and safety of ourselves and our users. This includes the exchange of information with other companies and organization to avoid fraud and to reduce the risk of credit. In case of doubt, please read Section 5: Legal Disclaimer of the current Privacy Policy.

### 4.1 Non-Personal Aggregate Information.

We may share aggregate information with third parties, including reports generated as a result of your use of the Service, including non-identifiable information and login data, for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and other commercial purposes, like offering targeted advertising about other products and services.

Any aggregated information shared in these instances will not contain your Personal Information. We do not aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

### 4.2 Combined Information

We may combine certain Personal Information with non-personal Information in order to create information and services packages that better suit your interests and preferences. Among other things, linking that information will allow us to improve and personalize the Site and the Service.

If we combine or link any information with your Personal Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personal Information and this Policy will apply.

### 4.3 Disclosure of your information to other users.

Zeendo is not responsible for the personal information of other users, collected by the user through the use of the Service or the Site.

Any information that you may choose to share in a comment or submission to the Site or the Service will be publicly available and may allow for other users to know about you. We recommend that you preserve your privacy and sensitive information, and encourage you to carefully consider what kind of information about yourself you want to disclose in your comments and observations.

### 4.4 Change in ownership.

In the event that ZEENDO went through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or part of its assets, or in the event of bankruptcy, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information, so you will be able to exercise your ARCO rights if you deem it appropriate.

### 4.5 International assignment and transfer of data

Zeendo informs you that, in order to effectively perform our service, it may be necessary to assign your personal data to third parties, including international transfers to our server located in France. You hereby acknowledge and consent to the international transfer of your data.

The international transfers made by Zeendo are carried out according to the legislation in force, so Zeendo guarantees that the data transferred is stored, treated and used in countries whose data protection legislation is considered suitable by the Spanish legislation.

###  **5\. Legal Disclaimer**

Zeendo may keep, share, disclose your personally identifiable information with other companies, organizations or individuals outside Zeendo if so is required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website, and/or to inforce our Terms of Use of the Service.

###  **6\. Communications from ZEENDO**

### 6.1 Service-related Announcements

We may send you email announcements in relation with the Site, the Service or your products like, for instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance.

Although these are not commercial communications, if you do not wish to receive them, you can unsubscribe from these communications at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of the communication email.

### 6.2 Other Messages and Customer Service

Occasionally, we may also send you messages about new features or services that we offer to our users. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of the communication email.

When you issue a customer support request to Zeendo, we may use your information and email address to contact you regarding your inquiry.

###  **7\. Cookies**

Like most websites, we use small bits of data called cookies, stored on users' computers to simulate a continuous connection. Cookies let us 'remember' information about your preferences and passwords and allow you to move within our Service without reintroducing yourself. Users who disable cookies will not be able to use the Service, as they are required to maintain their login information in our service during a browsing session.

Disabling cookies does not prevent you from accessing the websites published in our system, although some features of those sites may not be available.

These cookies can be tied back to personally identifiable information only in the event that you are logged into our Service. If you are logged in to our Service, the cookies on your computer will only identify your account within our system.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Zeendo only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, such as advertisers.

###  **8\. Links to Other Sites**

This website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by ZEENDO. These links are in a format that enables to keep track of whether these links have been followed.

Please note that Zeendo is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

###  **9\. Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. The rights contained in this Privacy Policy related to users will never be limited under any circumstances. In case of substantial modification, user-clients will be notified by e-mail.

###  **10\. Contacting Us**

If you have any concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [www.zeendo.com/contact-us](http://zeendo.com/contact-us).

ZEENDO is located at:

ZEENDO – Product by Onbile, LLC.  
Av. Marqués de Sotelo, 1 Pta. 3  
46002 Valencia - SPAIN  
Email: [help@zeendo.com](mailto:help@zeendo.com)
